Okay, we're gonna go ahead and get
started. Uh, go ahead Ryan, you can go.
>> Hey, Traden. This is Ryan McFat from
ESPN. First of all, welcome to Las
Vegas. My question for you is, what were
your interaction like with the Raiders
during the pre-draft process? Like, how
many visits did you have with us through
the combine or 30 visit? Just could you
talk to us through your interaction with
the Raiders um during the pre-draft
process?
>> Yeah. Um, you know, I had a chance to
sit down with them in the formal and,
you know, that went really well. Um, I
had a chance to connect with some of the
coaches and stuff. Um, after that, you
know, I didn't I didn't hear much. Um,
and you know, sometimes that's how it
goes in the process. And, uh, but I'm
super excited to be here and super
excited to get to work with these
coaches and and some of the some of the
players on this on this squad already.
>> Congratulations on being a Raider. This
is Hondo Carpenter from OSI. And I
wanted to give you just your thoughts.
You, you know, they announced you as a
safety and your speed is overwhelming.
It's extremely fast. But you are also a
hitter. You're a thumper. You like to
get up there like a linebacker. Can you
talk about that unique mix of speed and
highly aggressive
nature of play, please?
>> Yes, sir. Um, you know, I think, uh, the
the the speed is come comes from a, you
know, physical standpoint. You know,
working out hard and training my whole
life, honestly. Um, and then I think,
um, you know, bringing that bringing
that thump, like you said, is kind of
more of a mentality. Um, and you know, I
decide to go out there and play with
that mentality every time. And you know,
it's helped me elevate my game to the
next level. And I I can't wait to, you
know, keep keep expanding on that, keep
building it at this next level.
>> Hey, what's up, man? This is Adam Hill
from the Las Vegas Review Journal. Uh,
you played a ton of outside corner early
in your career. Uh, played some safety,
played nickel. What do you see your role
being at the next level?
>> Yeah, I mean, I'm I'm I'm willing to
play any of them. like you said, you
know, I got I got some good reps at at
every every pretty much every defensive
back position. Um, so what whatever the
coaches want me at, whatever the coaches
see me fitting best, um, I'm I'm willing
to do and, you know, whatever I can play
to help the team win games, that's where
I'm at.
>> Hey, Trey, how you doing? Q Myers here,
Raider Nation Radio 920. Uh, getting
interceptions and PBUS is not on
accident. It's a skill set. What is it
that goes into the mindset and and and
what is it that makes you so good at
seeing the ball and getting the ball?
Yeah, I think uh like you said, mindset
is a huge part of that. Um, you know, I
think uh getting the ball back to your
offense is obviously going to be the the
most important thing you can do as a as
a defender. And you know, being a
defensive back, you get the most
opportunities in the pass game. And, you
know, that's how I think. You know,
every time that ball's in the air, I
want to get it back for our offense. Um
because scoring points wins games. And
if we can hold them to zero, all the
offense needs to do is score three
points and it's good. Um, so you know, I
think uh I think a lot of teams and you
know, honestly, football as a whole has
kind of recognized the value of
turnovers and uh I I value that as
highly as as anything um on the football
field.
>> Uh Traydan, what do you think it is
about you as a player and as a young man
that took you from being a walk-on uh at
Arizona all the way to this position now
pretty pretty high up in the draft early
in the second round in the NFL now?
Yeah, I think it all it all falls down
to my values. Um, you know, I kind of go
by a motto of heart. Um, it's humility,
efficacy, accountability, resilience,
and trustworthiness. Um, I've I've used
that those values at every level in
every stage of my life. Um, it's just
helped me grow and and keep uh striving
to be my best um in in all aspects of my
life. And, you know, right now football
is football is number one for me. And,
um, I'm I'm pouring everything I got
into football. And I think that's what's
allowed me to to have the growth that
I've had, you know, from from being a
walk-on till now.
>> Hey, traden Jesse Merrick with Silver
and Black Sports Network. I'm just
curious of your skill set. What do you
think, you know, translates the best to
what modern safeties are asked to do in
the NFL now?
>> Yeah, I think um you know, having the
the speed, range, and processing ability
um to to get to, you know, cover cover
ground on the field. Um, you know,
there's there's a lot of good
quarterbacks and a lot of fast receivers
and, you know, they they want those shot
plays and those are the plays that you
got to make if you want to win football
games. Um, and I think, uh, I'll be able
to come in and help the team, uh, defend
those type of type of shot plays and and
make plays on the football when I get a
chance.
>> Hey, congratulations. Going from a
walk-on to a second round pick, when did
you realize that this was possible for
you? And when did you know you you set
the NFL as your goal?
>> Yeah, I mean the NFL has been my goal as
long as far back as I can remember. Um
but you know I think it it became
realistic for me uh probably around my
junior season. Um, you know, I realized
that, you know, the game was kind of
slowing down for me and I I was playing
at a level where I felt like, you know,
I could compete with anybody in the
country. And, um, you know, I I had a a
couple setbacks even from then. Um, but
I never I never wavered in my trust and
in my values. And I think, uh, it
allowed me to just keep that keep that
mentality knowing uh, you know, the
player I am, the person I am, that I'm
I'm ready to compete at the highest
level and uh, you know, help a team win
a Super Bowl. What do you think people
got wrong about you?
>> Um,
I don't know. I mean, I I was, you know,
I was I was a little underrecruited. Um,
I think I don't think everyone knew how
fast I was. I don't think they knew I
was that fast. Um, so running the 433,
it was was fun. That was cool.
>> Thank you.
>> It's Hondo Carpenter again. I'm going to
give you a chance to brag on your elma
mater, but they believed in you and you
really developed there under the
coaching. Will you talk about what
Arizona has meant to you and just quite
frankly the quality of coaching that you
got there that saw you go from a walk-on
to a highly valued top end second
rounder?
>> No, absolutely no. I got a lot of love
for Arizona. Um, you know, I grew from a
boy to a man, you know, in my time over
there. And, um, you know, my path wasn't
exactly perfect. U, you know, we had
three head coaches, five defensive
coordinators. Uh, but I I saw that as a
blessing. you know, I got to pick pick
knowledge from five different, you know,
high level coaches. I had, you know,
different position coaches throughout
all those times. And, um, you know, I've
got to pick the brains of a lot of high
level football coaches. And, um, I think
the ones that they have in the building
now are fantastic developers. Um, they
do it the right way. You know, it's not
it's not about the money or this and
that. Um, you know, they they're they're
bringing you in. They're going to try to
develop you. And, you know, you can see,
you know, the the rewards of of having a
you know, having a staff like that. We
got three safeties that are going to be
drafted this year. So, um, if anyone's
if anyone's looking out there trying to
trying to get right, go to Arizona, man.
>> Hey, Trey, you were a 4.0 student in
high school. Uh, graduated two years
ago, academic, all Big 12. How how much
is your intelligence, your brain kind of
played into your development, and it
helps you on the football field?
>> No. Yeah, 100%. Uh, we used to have a
coach that say the days of the dumb jock
are over. Um, and it's it's very true.
Um, you know, you have to be a smart you
have to be smart to play high level
football. There's a lot of moving parts.
There's a lot of things going on and if
you want to be able to keep up and
adjust um in real time um you gota you
got to have the brain processing power
to do so especially playing you know
safety or the quarterback of the
defense. So, um, yeah, I think, uh, you
know, just just having, you know, that
that higher intellect and, you know,
keep continuing to train my brain, um,
just helps me process things faster and,
you know, digest and, um, do different
things on the field and, you know, be
able to be able to like make those
real-time decisions, snap decisions in
in in seconds.
>> Hey, Sam Warren with the Athletic. Um,
can you talk a little bit about your
leadership qualities? thought I read
that you're a three-time uh team
captain, helped coach the team a little
bit when you torn your ACL. Like, how do
you how do you approach being a leader
on a team? And what do you expect kind
of that role to be like when you go to
the Raiders?
>> Yeah. Um, no, I I did have a chance to
be a three-time captain over there. That
was, you know, a really proud moment for
me and proud past few years. Um, I was
never a really out there like speech guy
or anything like that, but um, I did
take it very seriously when I got voted
captain for the first time. And um you
know I I try to you know develop those
leadership skills that you know that you
can have because I think it's you know
it's just it's a trait and it's a skill
that you can practice at. And you know
just just learning from that learning
you know everything that I got. I I'll
be able to go into a locker room and you
know get get to know the guys get to
know the people that have been doing it
for some years and u you know learn from
them and whenever my time comes to step
up and be that leader like I I' I've got
some experience at that so I can do it.
and train. Uh any guys in particular
that you modeled your game after?
>> Um not necessarily modeled. Um I would
say like I I'm a fan of of of a few guys
how they play the game and you know what
they're able to do on the field like
guys like uh like Kyle Hamilton or um
Cooper Deene, Jaylen Petri, those type
of guys. Um you know I really respect
the way that they go about their
business and the way that they you know
they they show up on Sundays. Um, so but
I'll say, you know, my game's kind of a
little bit different from all of theirs.
It's it's it's kind of a unique style of
football.
>> Last one, Levi Edwards. Go ahead.
>> Yes. If obviously to walk on to Arizona,
if you had to give any advice to the
former self, you know, coming up through
that process or any young player that
had to go through what you went through
to get to where you are, what would it
be?
>> Yeah. Um, I mean, yeah, you kind of
talked about the process. I would say,
you know, in short, I would say just
trust the process. Um, you know, kind of
understand that, you know, being a walk-
on it is a little bit different. You're
going to have to work a little harder.
You're going to have to show up when
when you get your opportunity and, um,
just be be prepared for that moment.
Don't don't let it, you know, come and
go. Um, it's like it's football is all
preparation and, you know, if you if you
are going about all your business the
right way, when you get that
opportunity, you you got to be there to
show up and and go get it. And um I
think anybody's capable of it. You know,
if a guy like me with zero stars out of
high school can can make it to this
point, anybody is capable of doing
whatever they want. You know, if it if
they are disciplined and they put in the
work and effort that it takes um to to
be prepared for for their moment to
shine.
>> Awesome. Thanks, Ten. Appreciate you.
>> Thank you guys. I appreciate you having
me.